Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series LIII is arranged in 8 sub-series by Union file number.
Series LIV is arranged in 71 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series LIII. GRAND EXECUTIVE BOARD
  - Sub-Series 325-0. Grand Executive Board
    - General, 1923-1959 (Box 507, Folder 34)
    - General, 1925 (Box 507, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 325-1. Grand Executive Board
    - Financial Assistance, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 325-2. Grand Executive Board
    - Minutes, 1924 (Box 507, Folder 37)
    - Minutes, 1925 (Box 507, Folder 38)
    - Minutes, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 325-3. Grand Executive Board
    - Railway Employees' Department, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 325-4. Grand Executive Board
    - Union Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 325-6. Grand Executive Board
    - 1924 Court Action, 1924-1925 (Box 507, Folder 42)
    - 1924 Court Action, 1925 (Box 507, Folder 43)
    - 1924 Court Action. Newspaper Clippings, 1924-1925 (Box 507, Folder 44)
    - 1924 Court Action, 1924-1925 (Box 507, Folder 45)
    - 1924 Court Action, 1925 (Box 507, Folder 46)
    - 1924 Court Action, 1926 (Box 507, Folder 47)
    - 1924 Court Action (Box 507, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series 325-7. Grand Executive Board
    - Minutes, 1924 (Box 507, Folder 49)
  - Sub-Series 325-8. Grand Executive Board
    - Per Diem and Expenses, 1925 (Box 507, Folder 50)
- Series LIV. 1922 CONVENTION
  - Sub-Series 326-0. 1922 Convention
    - General, 1924 (Box 507, Folder 51)
  - Sub-Series 326-1. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 1, 1922-1924 (Box 507, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 326-2. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 2, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 326-3. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 3, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 54)
  - Sub-Series 326-4. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 4, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 55)
  - Sub-Series 326-5. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 5, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 56)
  - Sub-Series 326-6. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 6, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 57)
  - Sub-Series 326-7. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 7, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 58)
  - Sub-Series 326-8. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 8, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 59)
  - Sub-Series 326-9. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 9, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 60)
  - Sub-Series 326-10. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 10, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 61)
  - Sub-Series 326-11. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 11, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 62)
  - Sub-Series 326-12. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 12, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 63)
  - Sub-Series 326-13. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 13, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 64)
  - Sub-Series 326-14. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 14, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 65)
  - Sub-Series 326-15. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 15, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 66)
  - Sub-Series 326-16. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 16, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 67)
  - Sub-Series 326-17. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 17, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 68)
  - Sub-Series 326-18. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 18, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 69)
  - Sub-Series 326-19. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 19, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 70)
  - Sub-Series 326-20. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 20, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 71)
  - Sub-Series 326-21. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 21, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 72)
  - Sub-Series 326-22. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 22, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 73)
  - Sub-Series 326-23. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 23, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 74)
  - Sub-Series 326-24. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 24, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 75)
  - Sub-Series 326-25. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 25, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 76)
  - Sub-Series 326-0. 1922 Convention
    - Proceedings, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 77)
      1922 May 13
    - Report of Vice Grand Presidents, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 78)
    - Proceedings, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 79)
    - Proceedings, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 80-81)
      1922 May 12
    - Proceedings, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 82-83)
      1922 May 10
    - Proceedings, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 84-85)
      1922 May 9
    - Proceedings, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 86-87)
      1922 May 8
    - Proceedings, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 88-89)
      1922 May 6
    - Proceedings, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 90)
      1922 May 1
    - Proceedings, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 91-92)
      1922 May 5
    - Proceedings, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 93-94)
      1922 May 4
    - Proceedings, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 95-96)
      1922 May 3
    - Proceedings, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 97-98)
      1922 May 2
    - Proceedings, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 99)
    - Proceedings, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 100)
      1922 May
    - Report of Grand Secretary-Treasurer, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 101-103)
    - Report of Editor and Business Manager of The Railway Clerk, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 104-107)
    - Report of Board of Directors, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 108-111)
    - Report of FitzGerald, E.H., Grand President, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 112-115)
    - Report of Vice Grand Presidents, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 116-120)
    - Report of Committee on Resolutions, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 121-123)
    - Proceedings, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 124-128)
    - Amendments to Constitution Submitted by Delegates, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 129-130)
    - Report of Forrester, J.J., Grand President, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 131-133)
    - Report of Committee on Legislation, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 134-136)
    - Resolutions, 1922 (Box 507, Folder 137)
    - General, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 326-26. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 26, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 326-27. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 27, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 326-28. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 28, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 326-29. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 29, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 326-30. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 30, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 326-31. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 31, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 326-32. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 32, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 326-33. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 33, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 326-34. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 34, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 326-35. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 35, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 326-36. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 36, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 326-37. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 37, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 326-38. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 38, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 326-39. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 39, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 326-40. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 40, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 326-41. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 41, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 326-42. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 42, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 326-43. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 43, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 326-44. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 44, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 326-45. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 45, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 326-46. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 46, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 326-47. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 47, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 326-48. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 48, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 326-49. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 49, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 326-50. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 50, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 326-51. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 51, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 326-52. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 52, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 326-53. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 53, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 326-54. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 54, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 326-55. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 55, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 326-56. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 56, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 326-57. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 57, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 326-58. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 58, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 326-59. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 59, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 326-60. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 60, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 326-61. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 61, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 326-62. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 62, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 326-63. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 63, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 326-64. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 64, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 326-65. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 65, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 326-66. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 66, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 326-67. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 67, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 326-68. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 68, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 326-69. 1922 Convention
    - Resolution No. 69, 1922 (Box 508, Folder 45)